Dave: It’s really hot. Would you like a drink? Or an ice cream?
Becca: Yes, good idea. Let’s go to the café.
Dave: What kind of ice cream do you want?
Becca: Er, a Magnum, please.
Dave: Here you are. One Magnum.
Becca: Thanks, Dave.
Dave: Where do you live?
Becca: Very near here, in Park Road. And you?
Dave: I live quite near, in Queen’s Road.
What do you do, Becca?
Becca: I’m a journalist.
Dave: Really? How interesting! Do you work for a newspaper?
Becca: No, for TV. What about you?
Dave: I’m a teacher. I’m on holiday now.
Becca: Me too. Oh! My ice cream.
Dave: Dolly! Bad dog! I’m really sorry.
Becca: That’s OK.
Dave: Do you want another ice cream?
Becca: No, thanks.
Dave: Are you sure? I’m really sorry.
Look, let’s have lunch one day. Are you free on Saturday?
Becca: Oh, well, OK then. Yeah. Thanks very much.